Guide to the Stanford University, Computer Science Department, HCI Group, CS547 Seminar Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videorecordings
  - Ten Myths of Multimedia Interaction, Sharon Oviatt, Oregon Graduate Institute, 1999-2-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Sharon Oviatt, Oregon Graduate Institute, "Ten Myths of Multimedia Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1999-2-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - The Internet at Home: Expectations, Realities, and the Future, Sara Kiesler, Carnegie Mellon University, 1999-2-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Sara Kiesler, Carnegie Mellon University, "The Internet at Home: Expectations, Realities and the Future" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1999-2-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Personal Information, Privacy and the Web, Rob Barrett, IBM Almaden Research, 1999-3-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rob Barrett, IBM Almaden Research Center, "Personal Information, Privacy and the Web" (CS547 Winograd 10), 1999-3-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - The National Tele-Immersion Initiative, Jaron Lanier, National Tele-Immersion Initiative, 1999-3-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jaron Lanier, National Tele-immersion Initiative, "The National Tele-Immerson Initiative" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1999-3-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Computational Design, Mihai Nadin, University of Wuppertal, 1999-4-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Mihai Nadin, University of Wuppertal (Currently Stanford CSLI), "Computational Design" (CS547 Winograd 3), 1999-4-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Visual Interactive Simulations, Larry Tesler, David Canfield Smith, Allen Cypher StageCast, 1999-4-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Larry Tesler, Dave Smith, Allen Cypher, StageCast, "Visual Interactive Simulations" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1999-4-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Transcending the Individual Human Mind, Gerhard Fischer, University of CO, Boulder, 1999-4-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gerhard Fischer, University of Colorado, Boulder, "Transcending the Individual Human Mind" (CS547 Winograd 4), 1999-4-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Flatland User Interfaces, Anthony LaMarca, Xerox PARC, 1999-4-30; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Keith Edwards & Anthony Lamarca, Xerox PARC, "Flatland User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 5), 1999-4-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Fluid Documents: Annotations in Context, Polle Zellweger, Xerox PARC, 1999-4-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Polle Zell Weger, Jock Macinlay, Bay-Wei Chang, Xerox PARC, "Fluid Documents: Annotation in Context" (CS547 Winograd 2), 1999-4-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Tacit Interaction, Elin Ronby Pederson, Google Research, 1999-5-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Elin Ronby Pederson, at Google Research, "Tacit Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 7), 1999-5-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Roomware: Towards the Next Generation of Human-Computer Interaction based on an Integrated Design of Real and Virtual Worlds, Nobert Streitz, GMD-IPSI, Darmstadt, Germany, 1999-5-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Norbert Streitz, GMD-IPSI, Darmstadt, Germany, "Roomware: Towards the next Generation of Human-Computer Interaction based on an Integrated Design of Real and Virtual Worlds" (CS547 Winograd 8), 1999-5-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Tasking Communities of Agents Through Adaptable Multimodal Interfaces, Adam Cheyer, SRI International, 1999-5-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Adam Cheyer, SRI International, "Tasking Communities of Agents Through Adaptable Multimodal Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 9), 1999-5-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Invisible Interfaces, Ken Fishkin, Xerox PARC, 1999-5-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ken Fishkin, AnuJ Gujar, Beverly Harrison & Roy Want, Xerox PARC, "Invisible Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 6), 1999-5-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Introduction to Haptics, Kenneth Salisbury, Stanford Dept. of Computer Science and Surgery, 1999-9-24; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kenneth Salisbury, Stanford, Departments of Computer Science and Surgery, "Introduction to Haptics" (CS547 Winograd 1), 1999-9-24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Jenny Preece, University of Maryland, "Online Communities: Design Usability, Supporting Sociability" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2000-10-13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Ben Shneiderman, University of Maryland, "Leonardo's Laptop: Human Needs and the new Computing" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2000-10-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Jennifer Healey, MIT Media Lab, "Sensible Computers: Technologies the Enable Computers to Understand Human Emotion" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2000-10-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Steve Shafer, Microsoft Research, "Easyliving: An Architecture for Building Intelligent Environments" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2000-10-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Kai Li, Princeton University, "Building a Scalable Display Wall" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2000-11-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Brad Johanson, Francois Guimbretiere, Terry Winograd, Stanford Computer Science, "Experiments in Interaction with Wall Displays" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2000-11-17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Ted Selker, MIT Media Lab, "Context Aware Computing; Can implicit communication with computers be more useful that explict communication?" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2000-11-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - The Importance of Homes in Technology Research, Debby Hindus, Interval Research, 2000-1-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Debby Hindus, Interval Research, "The Importance of Homes in Technology Research" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2000-1-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Cliff Nass, Department of Communication, Stanford Univeristy, "Voice Activated: Interface Design and the psychology of Enjoyment, Trust, and Sales" (CS547 Winograd), 2000-12-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Conversation Map: An Interface for Very Large Scale Conversations, Warren Sack, MIT Media Lab, 2000-1-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Warren Sack, MIT Media Lab, "Conversation Map: An Interface for Very Large Scale Conversations" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2000-1-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Buliding Novel Interfaces, Sidney Fels, University of British Columbia, 2000-12-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Sidney Fels, University of British Columbia, "Building Novel Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd), 2000-12-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Advanced Interface Design for Ease of Use, Tony Temple, IBM, 2000-1-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Tony Temple, IBM, "Advanced Interface Design for Ease of Use" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2000-1-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Better CHI through Digital Processing (People Centric Processing), Malcom Slaney, Interval Research, 2000-1-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Malcom Slaney, Interval Research, "Better CHI through Signal Processing (People Centric Processing)" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2000-1-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - In Support of Multimedia Conversations, Gregg Wolff, Ricoh Silicon Valley, 2000-2-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Greg Wolff, Ricoh Silicon Valley, "In Support of Multimedia Conversations" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2000-2-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Factors in Advanced Air Transportation Technologies, Richard Mogford, NASA Ames Research Center, 2000-2-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Richard Mogford, NASA Ames Research Center, "Human Factors in Advanced Air Transportation Technologies" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2000-2-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Effects of Humor in Task-oriented Human-Computer Interaction and Computer-Mediated Communication, John Morkes, Trilogy, 2000-2-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - John Morkes, Trilogy, "Effects of humor in Task-Oriented Human-Computer Interaction and Computer-Mediated " (CS547 Winograd 8), 2000-2-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Gender and Technology: A Case Study, Brenda Laurel, 2000-2-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Brenda Laurel, "Gender and Technology: A Case Study" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2000-2-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Social Tele-embodiment: Understanding Presence, Eric Paulos, UC Berkeley, 2000-3-10; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Eric Paulos, UC Berkeley, "Social Tele-embodiment: Understanding Presence" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2000-3-10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Designing with Haptic Feedback, Karon Maclean, Interval Research, 2000-3-3; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Karon Maclean, Interval Research, "Designing with Haptic Feedback" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2000-3-3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Engagement, Marney Morris, Animatrix, 2000-3-31; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Marney Morris, Animatrix, "Engagement" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2000-3-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - HWI: Human-Wearable Interaction, Vaughan Pratt, Stanford CS, 2000-4-14; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Vaughan Pratt, Stanford CS, "HWI: Human-Wearable Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2000-4-14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - The Task Gallery: a 3D Window Manager, Dan Robbins, Microsoft Research, 2000-4-21; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Dan Robbins, Microsoft Research, "The Task Gallery: A 3D Window Manager" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2000-4-21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - The Making of "GUI Bloopers", Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, Inc, 2000-4-28; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, Inc, "The Making of 'GUI Bloopers'" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2000-4-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Spoken User Interfaces, Bob Carpenter, SpeechWorks International, 2000-4-7; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Bob Carpenter, SpeechWorks International, "Spoken User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2000-4-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - New Findings on Facial Affects, Diane Schiano, Interval Research, 2000-5-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Diane Schiano, "New Findings on Facial Affects" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2000-5-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Psychological Arousal and Interactive Media, Byron Reeves, Stanford Dept. of Communication, 2000-5-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Byron Reeves, Stanford Deot. of Communication, "Psychological Arousal and Interactive Media" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2000-5-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - An Overview of oIBM Almaden Research Center's BlueEyes Project, Myron Flickner, IBM Almaden Research, 2000-5-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Myron Flickner, IBM Almeden Research, "An overview of IBM Almaden Research Center's BlueEyes Project" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2000-5-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - The Scent of a Sight: A System for Analyzing and Predictng information Scent, Usage, and Usability of a Web Site, Ed Chi, Xerox PARC, 2000-5-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ed Chi, Xerox PARC, "The Scent of a Sight: A System for Analyzing and Predicting Information Scent, Usage and Usability if a Web Site" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2000-5-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Scott Snibbe, "Haptic Techniques for Media Control" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2001-10-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Kristen Nygaard, University of Oslo, "A process-oriented conceptual platform for informatics" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2001-10-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - David Hilbert, Jonathan Trevor, FX-PAL, "M-Links: A UI For Web Interaction On Very Small Devices" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2001-10-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Jef Raskin, "Prolegomena to future interface design" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2001-10-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Gene Golovchinsky, FX-PAL, "Reading Appliances and the Future of the Document Work" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2001-11-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Larry Arnstein, University of Washington, "Experiment Capture in the Biology Lab" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2001-11-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Opening the Design Process: Everday People in the Fuzzy Front End, Elizabeth Sanders, SonicRim and Ohio State University, 2001-1-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Elizabeth Sanders, SonicRim and the Ohio State University, "Opening the Design Process: Everyday People in the Fuzzy Front End" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2001-1-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Anne Balsamo, Matt Gorbet, Scott Minneman, Steve Harrison, Xerox PARC, "XFR: eXperiments in the Future of Reading" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2001-11-30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - David Dupouy, Sensiva, "Symbols as Universal User Interface" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2001-11-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - The Playful World: Interactive Toys and the Future of Imagination, Mark Pesce, USC, 2001-1-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Mark Pesce, USC, "The Playful World: Interactive Toys and the Future of Imagination" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2001-1-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - The Psychology of Ecommerce: Choice Overload and other Paradoxes, Paul Whitmore, E*Trade, 2001-1-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Whitmore, E*Trade, "The Psychology of Ecommerce: Choice Overload and other Paradoxes" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2001-1-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Sheelagh Carpendale, University of Calgary, "Elastic Presentation" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2001-12-7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Lifelong Kindergarten, Mitch Resnick, MIT Media Lab, 2001-2-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Mitch Resnick, MIT Media Lab, "Lifelong Kindergarten" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2001-2-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Emerging Interactive Expression Systems: Blurring Author and Audience, Steve DiPaola, Stanford University Digital Art Center, 2001-2-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Steve DiPaola, Stanford University Digital Art Center, "Emerging Interactive Expression Systems: Blurring Author and Audience" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2001-2-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - New Learning Environments, David Cavallo, MIT Media Lab, 2001-2-23; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - David Cavallo, MIT Media Lab, "New Learning Environments" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2001-2-23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Interactive Design in Digital Entertainment, Fabrice Florin, Sirius, 2001-2-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Fabrice Florin, "Interactive Design in Digital Entertainment" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2001-2-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Characters Everywhere, Barbara Hayes Roth, Stanford Knowledge Systems Lab Extempo Systems, 2001-3-16; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Barbara Hayes Roth, Stanford Knowledge Systems Lab Extempo Systems, "Characters Everywhere" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2001-3-16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Multimedia Research at Microsoft: Making Audio and Video First-Class Objects, Jonathan Grudin, Microsoft Research, 2001-3-2; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jonathan Grudin, Microsoft Research, "Multimedia Research at Microsoft: Making Audio and Video First-Class Objects" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2001-3-2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Experiments with Un-tethered Interaction, Turner Whitted, Microsoft Research, 2001-3-9; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Turner Whitted, Microsoft Research, "Experiments with Un-tethered Interaction" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2001-3-9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Programming Support for Natural Interaction, Jennifer Mankoff, Georgia Tech, 2001-4-13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Casablanca: Designing Social Communication Devices for the Home, Debby Hindus, 2001-4-20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Debby Hindus, "Casablanca: Designing Soical Communication Devices for the Home" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2001-4-20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Awareness on the Move: Desktop and Mobile Awareness Prototypes for Coordinating Contact, John Tang and James Begole, SUN Microsystems, 2001-4-27; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - James "Bo" Begole,SUN Microsystems, "Awareness on the move: Desktop and mobile awareness prototypes for coordinating contact" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2001-4-27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - wk#5665 (CS547 Winograd 2), 2001-4-31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Interpreting Information Requests in Context, Charlie Ortiz, SRI International, 2001-4-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Collaboration as Theory and Practice, Andreas Lunsford, Stanford Dept. of English, 2001-5-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Andrea Lunsford, Stanford Dept of English, "Collaboration as Theory and Practice" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2001-5-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Pervasive Interaction: Informal Tools for Designing Anywhere, Anytime, Anydevice User Interfaces, James Landay, UC Berkeley, 2001-5-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - James Landay, UC Berkeley, "Pervasive Interaction: Informal Tools for Designing Anywhere, Anytime, Anydevice User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2001-5-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Web Browsing on Handheld Devices, Orkut Buyukkoten, Stanford CS, 2001-5-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Orkut Buyukkokten, Stanford CS, "Web Browsing on Handheld Devices" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2001-5-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Jeff Johnson, UI Wizards, "Designing Responsive Software Despite Performance Limitations" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2001-5-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Fluid Interaction for High Resolution Wall-Size Displays, Francis Guimbretiere, Stanford CS, 2001-6-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Francois Guimbretiere, Stanford CS, "Fluid Interaction for High Resolution Wall-size Displays" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2001-6-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Dan Russell, IBM Almaden, "BlueBoards in Use: Large Public Displays for Collaboration" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2001-9-28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Desire in Context, Rich Gold, The Red Shift, 2002-10-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Rich Gold, The Red Shift, "Desire in Context" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2002-10-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Post-desktop User Interfaces, Jane Borchers, Stanford CS, 2002-10-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jane Borchers, Stanford Computer Science, "Post-desktop User Interfaces" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2002-10-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Handheld Usability, Scott Weiss, Usable Products Company, 2002-10-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Scott Weiss, Usable Products Company, "Handheld Usability" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2002-10-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Seven Slides and a Fight: How Extreme Progarmming Improved Our User-Centered Design Process, But Not Our Social Skills, Nicolas Ducheneaut, Mark Howard, Ian Smith, Victoria Bellotti, PARC, 2002-10-4; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Victoria Bellotti, PARC, "Seven Slides and a fight: How Extreme Programming improved out user-centered design process, but not our social skills" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2002-10-4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Marc Davis, UC Berkeley SIMS, "Towards Computational Media: Metadata for Media Automation and Reuse" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2002-11-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Google Is Not an Anomaly: A Blueprint for Inventing and Building Innovative and Successful User-centric Products, Larry Page, Google, 2002-1-11; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Larry Page, Google, "Google is not an anomaly: A blueprint for inventing and building innovative and successful user-centric products" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2002-1-11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Aaron Marcus, Aaron Marcus and Associates, "Vehicle User-Interface Design" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2002-11-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Brad Myers, Carnegie Mellon University, "Mobile Devices for Control" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2002-11-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Paul Whitmore, ETRADE, "Beginning with the End in Mind: How to Design for People's Real Goals" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2002-11-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Interactive Medical Education, Parvati, Dev, Stanford Summit, 2002-1-18; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Parvati Dev, Stanford Summit, "Interactive Medical Education" (CS547 Winograd 2), 2002-1-18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Visualization for All, Jock Mackinlay, Xerox PARC, 2002-1-25; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Jock Mackinlay, Xerox PARC, "Visualization for All" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2002-1-25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Electronic Chalk: A Tool for Live and Remote Teaching, Raul Rojas, Freie Universitaet Berlin, 2002-12-6; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Raul Rojas, Freie Universitaet Berlin, "Electronic Chalk: A tool for live and remote teaching" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2002-12-6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Utopian Entrepreneur, Brenda Laurel, 2002-2-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Brenda Laurel, "Utopian Entrepreneur" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2002-2-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - The Cybernetics of HCI, A Pragmatic Approach, Paul Pangaro, SUN Microsystems, 2002-2-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Paul Pangaro, SUN Mircosystems, "The Cybernetics of HCI, A Pragmatic Approach" (CS547 Winograd 6), 2002-2-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Interactive Workspace in Construction, Kathleen Liston, Stanford Civil Engineering, 2002-2-22; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Kathleen Liston, Stanford Civil Engineering (CIFE), "Interactive Workspace in Construction" (CS547 Winograd 7), 2002-2-22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Moore's Law Meets Physiology: The Future of Interactive Systems, Dan Olsen, Brigham Young University, 2002-2-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Dan Olsen, Brigham Young Univeristy, "Moore's Law Meets Physiology: The Future of Interactive Systems" (CS547 Winograd 5), 2002-2-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Input Research at Microsoft: Sensors, Mice and Keyboards, Oh My!, Ken Hinckley, Microsoft Research, 2002-3-1; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Ken Hinckley, Microsoft Research, "Input Research at Mircosoft: Sensors, Mice and Keyboards, Oh My!" (CS547 Winograd 8), 2002-3-1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Sparrow Web: Community Shared Web Pages, Eric Bier and Ken Pier, PARC, 2002-3-15; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Eric Bier, Ken Pier, PARC, "Sparrow Web: Community Shared Web Pages" (CS547 Winograd 10), 2002-3-15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Focus Plus Context Screens: Displays for Users Working with Large Visual Documents, Patrick Baudisch, PARC, 2002-3-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Hanging with Computers: The Role of IM in Teenage Communication, Rebecca Grinter, PARC, 2002-3-8; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Patrick Baudisch, Rebecca Grinter, PARC, "Focus Plus Context Screens: Displays for Users Working with Large Visual Documents", "Hanging with Computers: The Role of IM in Teenage Communication" (CS547 Winograd 9), 2002-3-8; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - TreadMill Ink -- Enabling Contniuous Pen Input on Small Devices, Giovanni Seni, Motorola Human Interface Labs, 2002-4-12; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Giovanni Seni, Motorola Human Interface Labs, "TreadMill Ink -- Enabling Continuous Pen Input on Small Devices"(CS547 Winograd 2), 2002-4-12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Social Creativity and Meta-Design in Lifelong-Learning Communities, Gerhard Fischer, University of Colorado, 2002-4-19; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Gerhard Fischer, University of Colorado, "Social Creativity and Meta-Design in Lifelong Learning Communities" (CS547 Winograd 3), 2002-4-19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Coding with Motion: Perceptually Based Visualization Techniques, Lyn Bartram, Coligio, 2002-4-26; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Lyn Bartram, Coligio, "Coding with Motion: Perceptually based Visualization Techniques" (CS547 Winograd 4), 2002-4-26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Interaction Design at Pixar Animation Studios, Karon Weber, Pixar, 2002-4-5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 12)
  - Karon Weber, Pixar, "Interaction Design at Pixar Animation Studios" (CS547 Winograd 1), 2002-4-5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)